softlandmark.com 2018-05-14

# SoftLandMark Software - Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy: 

Privacy Statement

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. 

Collection of information

Certain technical information is collected, such as: 

  * how people are finding our web site 
  * what technologies are used to access it and what pages interest the visitors 
  * IP address, browser type and version, operating system and screen resolution 

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We do not collect personally identifiable information about our visitors without their consent. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.ï¿½ 

The collected information is used to:

  * Provide our visitors with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site 
  * Promote our software resources 
  * Customize the website according to visitorï¿½s interests, search engine requirements and marketing strategies 

The information collected is not shared with any other organization, nor is any information sold or bartered unless otherwise stated. 

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by using the [contact form](http://www.softlandmark.com/contact). 

External advertisements on our Website

Our site shows external advertising and links to other websites. No personally identifiable customer information is made available to these advertisers or third-party websites. The advertisers generally store cookies on visitor's computers to record information including which advertisement they followed to reach the advertiser's website, and the date when they visited. Depending on the advertiserï¿½s policy cookies are automatically deleted after a certain period of time. 

Google Adsense is also used to support our site. Ads provided by Google AdSense are relevant to the content of the website and / or page they are on (i.e. they retrieve the information from the website contents, not the visitors themselves). Google Adsense uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Googleï¿½s use of DART cookies enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to the current site and to other sites on the Internet. A user may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Information control

A person/organization publishing a posting in the corresponding website category of softlandmark.com is responsible for the contents of the posting. Please send all your questions or claims to the information provided to the appropriate Author or Company which has published the given information, not to softlandmark.com. 

Security

Our site contains links that you may follow to visit other sites. However, once you leave softlandmark.com we are no longer responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, therefore we cannot protect the privacy of any information provided while visiting these sites. You should be cautious and look at the privacy statement of the site you are on before providing any personally identifiable information. 

Privacy contact

If you believe that we should be notified on any issues concerning our privacy statement, please [contact us](http://www.softlandmark.com/contact).
